I'm going out to South Park gonna have myself a time
Friendly faces everywhere humble folks without temptation
I'm goin out to south park gonna leave my woes behind
Ample parking day or night people spouting howdy neighbor
I'm heading out to south park to see if i cant unwind
I like girls with big fat titties really big fat titties
So come on out to south park and meet some friends of mine
South Park - Season 11 Episode 6 "D-Yikes!"
所有人都他妈给我闭嘴，坐下！
Everyone, sit down and shut the fuck up!
真操蛋！
Goddamnit!
这些臭男人们，都是一丘之貉
Stupid ass man! They're all the same!
哦，天啊，又来了！
Oh God, here we go again.
所有男人都只关心性
All men care about is SEX!
我为那愚蠢的约会花了两个小时准备
I spent two hours getting ready for that stupid date!
可当那混蛋看到我的身体时，他居然说
And when the bastard checks out my body, he just says,
“嘿，你以前是个男人吗？”
"Hey, did you used to be a guy or somethin'?"
我现在是女人了，以前的事又怎么了？
I'm a woman now, so what's it matter?!
啊偶，不太妙啊
Uh oh, this isn't good.
我和你说话了吗，小崽子？！
Did I say something to you, sugartits?!
没有，夫人
No ma'am.
你们男孩就是让我讨厌
You boys make me sick!
你们迟早有一天会变成男人，
You're well on your way to being men,
只会用老二思考！
who only think with their penises!
我要给你们全部布置回家作业
I am assigning you all weekend homework!
你们得给我读完海明威的
You are going to read Hemingway's book,
“老人与海”
"The Old Man And The Sea"!
你疯了吗？
Have you lost your mind?
伙计，我们不可能在一个周末的时间读完一整本书
Dude, we can't read an entire book in one weekend.
哦，那太糟糕了，伙计
Oh, that's too bad, dude.
也许你们男孩学会怎么把自己小jj关在裤子里不让它到处惹事的话
Maybe if you boys could keep your penises in your pants
你们就能有足够的时间了
once in a while you'd get more done!
但是老师， 我的小jj从来没有溜出过裤子哦.
But Teacher, my penis never slips out of my pants.
呃，除了穿睡衣的时候有几次
Eh-except sometimes when I'm wearin' pajamas.
如果周一你们的论文还没写好的话,
If you do not have an essay written on Monday,
那就不及格! 都清楚了吗?!
then you will fail! Is that clear?!
伙计，我们怎么可能在一个周末读完一整本书
Dude, how are supposed to read an entire book
和写完论文
over the weekend and write an essay?
我们整个周末算是毁了
Our whole weekend is shot.
（我们他娘的怎么办捏？）
(What the hell are we going to do?!)
伙计们，伙计们，放轻松
You guys, you guys, relax.
我们不需要读这本书和写论文
We don't have to read the book or write the essay.
- 我们不需要？ - 不需要
- We don't? - No.
这世界上有种人叫枪手
There's people you can hire to do these sorts of things.
伙计们，伙计们
縌ue paso? 縌ue paso?
找工作吗？墨西哥佬
Looking for work? S? Trabajo?
- 是的 - 我们找工作
- Yeis. - We looking work, s?
好的，听好了，墨西哥佬， 我们需要你们帮我们读完
Okay, listen up, Mexicans. We need you to read
“老人与海”这本书，懂了吗？
"The Old Man And The Sea" for us. Comprende?
“老人与海” （墨西哥语）
"The Old Man Y La Mer.
好的，没问题，没问题
Okay. Sure. Okay. Yeah.
这里，我们需要你们读完这本书
Here. We need you to work together, read the book
然后写四篇论文，懂了吗？
and write four essays, comprende?
读后感（墨西哥语）
La samaraisia.
- 好的，没问题 - 是的，我们能完成
- Okay no problem. That's no problem. - Yeah, we can do that.
读后评论
S? la samuraisia.
- 好的，谢谢（墨西哥语） - 谢谢
- Okay, gracias. - Gracias.
伙计，这太酷了 我一点都不知道还可以这么搞
Dude, that is awesome. I had no idea you could do that.
哦，是的，有这些墨西哥佬真他娘的棒极了
Oh yeah, dude. Havin' Mexicans around totally kicks fuckin' ass.
都给我见鬼去吧
They can all rot in hell!
谁说没男人就不能活？
Who needs men anyway?!
他们只是一群该死的自大狂罢了
They're Goddamned arrogant self-centered assholes is what they are!
你没事吧，姐妹？
Are you okay, hon?
我只是讨厌男人罢了
I just hate men is all.
他们衡量女人的唯一标准就是你长的性不性感
It's like all they care about is how hot you look!
是的，我也从来不喜欢男人
Yeah, I've never been into men.
这就是为什么我来这里健身
That's why I work out here.
因为这里只有女人，可以不被男人色迷迷的盯着
Since it's women only we don't get ogled at or feel self-conscious.
深有同感
Tell me about it!
在那些混合健身房我连伸展运动都不能做
I can't even stretch at a normal gym
老有男人盯着我的乳沟
without some guy trying to stare down my vage.
我是 Allyson.
I'm Allyson.
哦，我是Janet. Janet Garrison.
Oh, I'm Janet. Janet Garrison.
对不起，我心情不太好
Sorry I'm so pissed off.
没关系的，我喜欢
No, I like it.
你看上去是个强壮的女人啊
You seem like a very strong woman.
是，很多人都这么说
Yeah, I've been told that.
我怎么从来没看见你去女生酒吧？
How come I've never seen you down at the girl bar?
女生酒吧? 我从不知道有这么个地方
Girl bar? I never even knew there was such a place.
喔，你会喜欢那的。那是镇上唯一一个
Oh you'd love it. It's the only bar in town
像我们这种女人能做回自己的地方
where women like us can hang out and be ourselves.
名字叫“蕾丝堡”
It's called "Les Bos."
Hi Linda, hi Kate.
Hey Allyson.
这个新来的女的是谁？
Who's the new girl?
Allyson总是喜欢强壮型的
Allyson always goes for the butch ones.
Hey Nell. 过的好吗, Tracy?
Hey Nell. What's up, Tracy?
这地方太棒了
Oowhat a great place.
这里的女的好像都互相很熟吗
All the girls here seem to know each other.
是啊，这里大多数的女的互相都做过
Yeah. Well, most of the girls here have done each other.
咿呀，做什么？
He-yeah. Done what?
你知道的啦，做爱啊
You know. Had sex.
啊，天哪！这里是个女同酒吧??
Oh my God, this is a lesbian bar??
是啊，我以为你早就知道呢。。。
Yeah. I... thought you understood that.
哦，上帝啊
Oh jeez.
对不起，我以为你知道“女生酒吧”的含义
I'm sorry. I thought you knew what "girl bar" meant.
但是我不是一个。。。哇啊
But I'm not a- ...whoa! Who-o-o-o-oa.
Janet, 真的对不起 只是在那体育馆里
Janet, I'm really sorry. It's just that at the gym
你说你不喜欢和男人在一起，所以我以为
you said you didn't like being with men, so I thought you were a-
我是不喜欢和男人在一起
I don't like being with men!
他们全都是些自私的蠢猪!
They're perverted selfish pigs!
那你。。有没有想过。。。和个女人在一起？
Have you... never even... thought... of being... with another woman?
欧，天啊，没有
Oho goodness no!
我当然没有这种念头
Of course I haven't.
其实说真的我还根本不知道
I mean... really I don't even understand
两个女的如何做爱
how two women can make love.
我想，她们只能通过剪抱式摩擦吧
I mean un, unless they just kinda scissor or something.
有很多做爱的方法, Janet.
There are a lot of ways to make love, Janet.
我不得不承认
I guess I'd be lying
我现在有些心痒痒的
if I said I wasn't a little ...titillated.
我能吻你吗？
Could I... maybe kiss you?
噢，这是不对的!
Oh, this is wrong!
我们都是女人，这不合理！
You're another woman; it doesn't make sense!
真的吗, Janet? 放开自己吧
Is it wrong, Janet? Let your inhibitions go.
让我们过个愉快的夜晚
Let's just have fun tonight.
不要太多的顾虑，就是享受
No commitments. Just fun.
欧耶，磨我！
Oh yeah, scissor!
耶，磨我，Allyson!
Yeah, scissor me Allyson!
Janet, 你真浪！
Janet, you're crazy!
欧，热辣的磨!
Oh, this is hot scissoring!
欧，我的下面要起火了！
Ohh! Scissor me timbers!
他们最好把作业写好了
They'd better be done with the book reports!
还有15分钟就上课了
School starts in 15 minutes!
他们会做好的
They'll be done.
伙计们，伙计们
縌ue paso? 縌ue paso?
你们读过那本书了吗？
All right, did you read the book?
- 是的 - 是
- S? - S?
写的什么？ 老师问的话怎么回答？
What was it about? Ih-in case our teacher asks us.
这本书说的是一个老人，
Eet starts there the old man,
他的工作是捕鱼，
and his job is to catch the feesh,
所以他坐上一只小船，出海去抓鱼，
so he get in the boht, to try and catch feesh.
然后他抓到一条鱼，但是这鱼非常强壮
Saw he catch the feesh, but the feesh is very strong,
老人没法收线把鱼捞上来
so the old man, cannot reel in the feesh.
所以他和鱼在海里搏斗了几天
So then he fight the feesh. Some more.
最后他终于把鱼抓住了
And he finally catch the feesh.
他把鱼抓到了，那他就赚到钱了？
He catches the feesh so, then he can make money.
不，因为在回家的路上,
No, because on the way home,
鲨鱼来了，把鱼肉都吃了.
the sharks come and eat the feesh.
所以，他没有赚到钱.
And so, he no make money.
完了吗？这就是整个故事？
That's it, that's the whole story?
是的
S?
好吧，你们写了四篇论文了吗？
All right, did you write the four essays?
是的，都写好了
S? we all wrote eses for you.
- 太好了! - OK，给我们吧.
- All right! - Okay, let's have 'em.
给什么?
Have what?
你不是说你帮我们写好论文了吗
You said you all wrote essays.
它们在哪里?
Where are they?
我ese住在迈阿密 （由于语言关系，墨西哥人理解错了，ese和essay混淆）
Well, my ese lives in Miami.
按照你吩咐的，我写信给她了,
I wrote to him like you said,
但我想她还没收到信吧.
but I don't think he got the letter yet.
我也写给阿布儿开齐的ese了
I wrote my ese in Albuquerque
我给三个ese都写了信
I wrote three eses:
老家的, 丹佛的,
my ese back home, my ese in Denver,
而我在格伦佛的ese还给我回了信
and my ese in Glenwood even wrote me back.
"谢谢给我写信，ese."
"Thanks for writing me, ese."
啊偶。。。
(Uh oh...)
伙计，我们这下操蛋了!
Dude, we're totally fucked now!
我们他妈的干吗要付钱让你们给你们的朋友们写信?!
Why the hell would we pay you to write your friends?!
我们也是觉得有点奇怪.
We thought it was kind of strange.
这都是你的错，Cartman! 现在我们要不及格了!
This is your fault, Cartman! Now we're gonna fail!
走吧，还有10分钟就上课了
You guys, school starts in ten minutes!
狗娘养的！
Son of a bitch!
Clyde? Clyde! Hey hey Clyde!
你也没写评论，是吗?
You didn't finish your essay either, right?
不，我写好了.
No, I got it done.
Jimmy, 你的评论写好了吗？
Jimmy, did you finish your book report?
是的，我觉得很不错
Yeah. I feel pretty good about it. I finished my whole book report
我自己写了一遍
and, I got a really nice letter from my ese
还让我在U-haul的朋友给润色了一遍
who works down at the U-Haul.
- 日! - 我们死定了
- Crap! - We're dead.
哈罗，同学们.
Hello, class.
这是我的小桌子,
Here's my little desk,
还有我亲爱的小黑板
my nice lil' chalkboard ...
Mrs. Garrison, 关于我们的论文。。。
Mrs. Garrison, about our book reports...
噢 没关系的 Eric
Oho, that's okay Eric.
如果你需要多一点时间处理你的家庭作业， 只需要说一下就可以了
If you need a little more time with your homework, just say so.
真的吗?
Really?
孩子们, 我需要告诉你们一件事
Kids, I need to tell you something
或许你们会很震惊
that you might find shocking.
我是同性恋
I'm gay.
又一次?
Again?
我一开始也相当震惊
It was a shock to me too.
我遇到了另一个女人
I... met another woman and...
我们去了一间叫蕾丝堡的奇妙的酒吧
we went to this fabulous bar called Lesbos
在那我就感觉在家一样
where I finally felt at home.
Allyson和我聊着聊着，我们就互相打开了心扉
Allyson and I talked, and really opened up to each other and...
然后我们...  磨了一个晚上.
then we...  scissored all night long.
摩擦的时候要小心
You have to be careful with scissors.
但是，听着, 我并没有要和Allison发展什么关系
But listen, I am not going to just rush into a relationship with Allyson.
我这么晚才发现我是女同
I'm a late-in-life lesbian.
所以我要好好尝试一下各种滋味，不是吗？
So I need to play the field for a while, right?
我实在太高兴了
Oh I'm so happy.
太棒了!
That's great!
让我们为老师变成女同欢呼！
Let's hear it for Teacher being a lesbian!
YAY!
Hey Tracy, hey Kate.
Hi Janet.
看上去好正啊, Linda.
Lookin' hot, Linda.
待会想去什么地方磨一下吗？
Wanna go somewhere and scissor later on?
啊?
Huh?
Hey Patty.
什么事, Janet.
What's up, Janet.
哦，不要这样看我.
Ooo, stop giving me that look.
就像用眼神在磨我.
Scissoring me with your eyes.
Hey Janet,你干嘛不去找个自己的女伴？
Hey Janet, why don't you pick up on your own girl?
哦, 想打架吗!
Oh yeah, dyke fight!
你踢中我的阴门了!
You kicked me right in the pussy!
欧，欧，我们在磨？ 欧耶，磨吧！
Uh? Oh! Oh, we're scissoring. Oh yeah, scissor!
你们两个，你们两个，停下
You guys. You guys, stop it.
大家听我说
Listen to me, everybody.
我有些坏消息
I got some bad news.
怎么了, Katie?
What is it, Katie?
他们要关了这个酒吧  永久的!
They're closing down the bar. For good!
关了酒吧？他们不能这么做
Closing it down? They can't do that.
这可是我们的家啊.
This is our home.
是啊，这是我们的家
Yeah, this is our home.
哎，是真的,我刚和酒吧老板谈过
Well it's true, I just talked to the owners.
他们要吧这个酒吧卖给波斯人
They've sold the bar to Persians.
波斯人？
Persians?!
那我们能去哪里呢？
So where are we supposed to go?
我们哪都不去！
We aren't going anywhere!
这有我们的历史！
We have a history here!
除非我死了，否则波斯人别想关掉这酒吧
Persians are closing this bar over my dead lesbian body!
市长，这是暴行啊！
Mayor, this is an outrage!
我们女同竟然受到如此歧视和欺凌！
We are being discriminated against as lesbians!
你现在是女同了？
You're a lesbian now?
没错，一个自豪的女同
That's right. A proud lesbian!
我们的家园正被霸占
And our home is being taken away!
酒吧被卖给了波斯业主
The bar has been sold to Persian club owners.
我不知道你们要我做点什么
I don't know what you want me to do about it.
禁止这笔交易！
Forbid the transaction!
这些事情一次又一次的发生，市长大人
This is happening all over the country, Mayor.
女同的酒吧被清空。。。被出售，这是不对的
Lesbian bars being bought out, shut down, it isn't right!
是啊，她说的很对！
Yeah, that's right!
对不起，我无能为力
I'm sorry, but my hands are tied.
新的业主决定明天重新装修酒吧
The new owners plan to start redecorating the bar tomorrow.
你们必须在那以前都清空
You have to be out by then.
你知道波斯人怎么装修的吗？
Have you seen how Persians decorate?
他们会在酒吧铺上劣质的蓝色的地毯，放上白色的雕像
They will cover that bar in cheesy blue carpeting, white statues
还有金色的窗帘，俗的看了就想吐
and gold curtain rods to the point that you will want to puke!
Mrs. Garrison, 请离开这里
Mrs. Garrison, get out of here.
这一杯是为了这里曾经的美好时光
Well, here's to some great times at this place.
没错，看来我们只能另外找个集会的地点了
Yeah. Guess we'll just have to find somewhere else to hang out.
现在，女伴们，我不能相信我听到了什么！我们不能放弃！
Now, come on gals ! I can't believe what I'm hearing ! We can't just give up !
- 我们应该怎么做呢, Janet? - 我们站出来斗争!
- What are we supposed to do, Janet? - We stand and fight!
波斯人来的时候，我们就告诉他们，我们不会离开蕾丝堡
When the Persians come we tell them "We aren't leaving Lesbos."
实际上，是蕾思堡
Actually, it's "Les Bos."
不，就是蕾丝堡
No, it's Lesbos!
我们就是蕾丝堡人！
We... are Lesbos!
作为蕾丝堡人，我们不能就这么站着看着
And as Lesbos, we cannot just stand and watch
一间间女同酒吧都被关掉
as one girl bar after another gets shut dowwwwwn!
波斯人派了一些人来谈判
The Persians have sent somebody to talk to us.
哈罗，我的名字叫 Emir Hadi.
Hello, my name is Emir Hadi.
我老板派我来，因为他听说
My boss sent me over here because he heard that you were upset
你们对我们接手这间酒吧很沮丧
about us trying to take over the bar.
- 是的 - 我们可以向你们保证
- Yes, we are. - Well, we want to assure you,
当这件酒吧变成波斯风格的时候
that when this place becomes another Club Persh,
你们依然得到100%的欢迎
you will all still be 100% welcome.
他们只是要把这地方改造一下而已
All they want is to make the place really nice.
我们将铺上蓝色的波斯地毯，金色的窗帘
We're going to put down some lovely blue carpet, and gold curtain rods.
我就知道！我就知道！
I knew it! I knew it!
但是依然欢迎你们啊
But you are still welcome to come.
我老板希望你们清楚，我们绝不会对女同性恋有任何歧视
My boss wants you to know that you will not be discriminated against in any way.
你们会允许其他非女同的人进来吗？还有男人？
Would you allow straight people in? Men?
哦。。我们会允许所有。。。
Well... we would allow whoev-
请小心你说的下一个词，波斯佬
Choose your next words wisely, Persian!
可是，我们没有任何义务只给女同提供服务
Look uhh, we don't have to offer you anything, so...
我不理解你为什么要态度这么恶劣，这简直是疯了
I don't know why you're being so difficult. This is crazy.
不，这一点也不疯
No, this isn't crazy.
这就是蕾丝堡人!
This... is... Lesbos!
你怎么能！
How dare you!
于是战争开始了.
And so it had begun.
往波斯使者蛋蛋上的这一脚，就是蕾丝堡人的宣战书.
By kicking the Persian messenger in the balls, the lesbos had sent a message.
全国的女同都听说了这勇敢的反抗
All over the country lesbians heard of the brave standoff.
在科罗拉多有一群自称为蕾丝堡人的女同性恋
As a group of lesbians in Colorado
正拼死守卫她们的女同酒吧
are refusing to allow the new owners of their bar in.
- 好样的! - 加油，姐妹们!
- Good for them! - You go girls!
波斯人回到了他们的办公室,
The Persians returned to their office,
告诉了他们的同事他们被30个蕾丝堡人挡在门外的故事
and told their coworkers how the thirty lesbos were refusing to let them in.
好的，如果他们30人要堵住门口
Well fine. If they're going to block the entrance,
我们就叫60个人去，我会在拉些波斯兄弟过来的
we'll just bring like, sixty of us! I'll call more Persians for help.
时间飞快的流逝着，蕾丝堡人勇敢地守在酒吧门口
The hours pass quickly, and the lesbians boldly stood out in front of their bar
不让波斯人踏入一步
to stop the Persians from entering.
他们来了
Here they come.
他们来了好多人啊
There's so many of them.
蕾丝堡人，摆好架势
Lesbos! Positions!
女同性恋们! 快让开吧 我们要进去重新装修了
Lesbians! Stand aside. We're coming in to redecorate it!
你们都去下地狱吧!你们可以用你们的蓝色地毯和金色窗帘
The hell you are! You can take your blue carpet and gold curtain rods
去堵上你们波斯佬的屁眼
and shove them up your Persian buttholes!
好吧！给我上！他们拦不住我们的
All right! Come on! They can't stop all of us!
蕾丝堡人，记住这一天！
Lesbos! Remember this day!
记住这一战！
Remember this fight!
一寸都不能相让！
Don't give them an inch!
嗷！伊朗变态男！
Ow! Iranian faggot!
说真的，让我们进去！
Come on, seriously, let us in!
绝不！
Never!
好几个小时过去了,蕾丝堡人一直阻挡着波斯人,
For hours, the Lesbos kept the Persians back,
把他们挡在门外， 挡住他们重新装修的计划
holding them off, keeping them from decorating.
终于波斯人精疲力尽了,
Finally the Persians grew tired,
很多波斯人想去逛街去选两幅最新式的太阳眼镜
and many of them wanted to go shopping for more designer sunglasses.
他们撤退了，蕾丝堡人守住了胜利
They retreated.  The Lesbos... had held.
蕾丝堡！
Lesbohhhs!!
那些没有去购物的波斯人
The Persians who did not go shopping
知道必须给他们老板一个交代
now knew they must face their boss.
他来了
Here he comes.
Rauf Xerxes. 他坐在一部纯金的悍马上面
Rauf Xerxes. He sat atop a gold Hummer
全身戴满了订制的只有波斯人才觉得酷的Gucci的首饰
with customized Gucci accessories which only a Persian would think was cool.
Mr. Xerxes, 蕾丝堡人不肯挪窝啊 我们没法子进去重新装修
Mr. Xerxes, the Lesbos wouldn't move. We could not get inside to redecorate.
Tumon, 你怎么连这么简单的任务都办不好？
Tumon, how could you have failed me in this simple task?
我现在真的很生气，我可以捏爆一个睾丸
I am so seriously pissed off right now. I could bust a testicle.
就在那时波斯老板意识到了
And with that the Persian club owner came to a realization.
我得亲自和这些蕾丝堡人谈谈
I shall have to deal with these lesbos myself.
姐妹们，我只是想说我太为你们骄傲了
Girls, I just want to say that I am very proud of you.
我们阻止了波斯人的这一战简直是太屌了
The way we kept those Persians from takin' over our bar was Les-tastic.
恩，是很棒，Janet 可是现在怎么办呢？
Well that's great, Janet, but what now?
我们不能待在这里档波斯人一辈子吧
We can't just stay here pushing them away our whole lives.
不能吗？我觉得很好玩啊
We can't? I think it's pretty fun.
我们必须有个更实际的计划
We have to have a more solid plan.
可以用来抵挡他们一辈子的计划
Something we can use against them permanently.
也许我们能想办法抓到这个老板的把柄
Maybe we can dig up some dirt on the club owner.
嘿，这是个好主意，我们需要一些人去打入他们内部
Hey, that's a great idea, Betsy. We need somebody working on the inside.
具体什么意思？
Whattaya mean?
如果我们能争取一些波斯人站在我们这边的话
If we could get some Persians on our side,
我们可以派他们过去打探老板的把柄
we could send them in to try to dig up some dirt on the owner!
可是谁能当这个间谍呢？我们不认识任何波斯人
But who's gonna spy on them for us? We don't know any Persians.
没问题，有些人你随时可以雇佣
It's okay. There's people you can hire for this kind of thing.
伙计们，伙计们
縌ue paso? 縌ue paso?
找工作吗，墨西哥佬？
Looking for work? S? Trabajo?
- 是 - 我们找工作
- Yeis. - We looking work, s?
好的，我们需要你们渗入波斯人内部
All right. We need you to infiltrate some Persians who run Club Persh,
打探隐私 抓住那个老板的把柄
and dig up some dirt on the owner.
OK，可以啊
Okay. Sure. Okay. Yeah.
Janet, 这怎么能成呢？他们看上去不像波斯人
Janet, how is this gonna work? They don't look Persian.
他们会的
Sure they do.
只需要抹点发胶
Just have to- gel the hair,
穿上件丝绸衬衫，戴根金项链
put on a silk shirt, some gold chains,
洒满古龙水
and tons of cologne.
波斯人
Persian.
看？
S?
WOW!
Wow!
好吧，墨西哥佬，其余人赶快化妆准备干活
All right, Mexicans, take the rest of these outfits
去看看你们能发现什么 地址就在里面
and see what you can find out. The address is in there too.
OK，没问题
Okay. No problem. Yes. S?
墨西哥人，摆脱快一点 我们的酒吧没多少时间了
And Mexicans, please hurry. Our girl bar has very little time.
一整天过去了，蕾丝堡人知道
A full day passed, and the Lesbos knew
波斯人的第二次进攻随时都可能发起
a second Persian attack was imminent.
在外面，蕾丝堡人一直紧密的监视着 随时准备发出警报
Outside, Lesbo lookouts kept watch, ready to alert the others.
蕾丝堡的老大在酒吧内坐立不安
The Lesbo leader sat nervously inside.
>她派墨西哥人装扮成波斯人去侦测的计划
>Her plan to dress Mexicans as Persians to act as spies,
也许已经失败了
perhaps it had failed.
她观察了下周围的蕾丝堡战友 他们都疲累不堪了
She looked around at her fellow Lesbos. They were tired.
为了保持蕾丝堡人的清醒，她没有别的选择
In order to keep her Lesbos awake, she had no choice:
她不得不去煮咖啡
she would have to make coffee.
由于咖啡的作用，蕾丝堡人仿佛重生了一般 但是她们能支撑多久呢？
With fresh coffee brewed, the Lesbos found new life, but would it be enough ?
那些波斯人又打过来了！
The Persians are attacking again!
- 做好准备，蕾丝堡人! - 出去决战!
- Take positions, Lesbos! - Get outside!
不，等等，等等，他们不是波斯人 是墨西哥人
No wait, wait! That's not the Persians, it's the Mexicans.
- 真的吗? - 你怎么知道?
- Really? - How can you tell?
让他们进来，没关系的
Let them through. It's okay.
- 你们好 - 你们好
- Hola, 緾髆o est醩? - Hola.
你们发现什么了吗？ 波斯人有在干什么违法的勾当吗？
Did you uncover anything? Are the Persians doing anything illegal?
哦，不，他们没有做任何非法的生意
Ahh, no. They're not doing anything illegal.
你们确定吗？
A-are you sure??
但是我们却发现了那个老板的一个小秘密。。。
No, but we did find out a kind of secret about the Persian in charge.
什么秘密？
What secret?!
- 哦，天啊，你们确定吗？ - 确定
- Oh my God, are you sure about this? - S?
Janet ! Janet, 那个波斯老板来了 他要和你单独谈一谈
Janet ! Janet, the Persian boss is here. He wants to talk to you and you alone.
没关系的，是时候去和这个波斯富佬面对面谈一下了
It's okay. It's time I met this rich Persian asshole face to face.
你们这些女同性恋为什么要这么难搞？
Why are you lesbians being so difficult?
因为我们在保护我们唯一的家
Because we're protecting the only home we have.
我不知道你们为什么要对这件事 这么小题大做
I don't know why you have to be all superlame about this.
你知道吗，很久以前，当我第一次知道我是个 女同性恋的时候
You know, a long time ago when I first realized I was a lesbian,
我感到傍徨和孤立
I felt isolated, confused.
只到我找到了这个能包容我，承认我的地方
And finally I found a place that accepts me for who I am.
OK，这样如何，我让你当这个酒吧的总经理
Okay, how about this? I will make you the manager of Club Persh.
你将有丰厚的薪水
You'll make good money.
这实在是个慷慨的提议, Xerxes.
That's a generous offers, Xerxes.
但是你知道吗，我知道你的一个小秘密
But you see, there's something I know about you.
我知道你实际上是个女人
I know you're actually a woman.
How did you find that out?
我雇佣了墨西哥人做间谍监视你
I hired Mexicans to spy on you!
他们看见你在“曲线美”健身
They saw you working out at Curves.
你不理解的，在波斯传统里面，女人不能当老板
You don't understand. Women can't be the boss in Persian culture.
这件事不能泄露给任何人
Nobody can know about this.
耶，你知道为什么吗？ 因为男人都是混蛋
Yeah. And you know why? Because men are all assholes!
不过因为你长的稍微高大和男性化了一点， 他们就百般嘲笑，羞辱你
They make you feel ashamed for being a little... big, or, manly looking.
但是蕾丝堡人不会，我们尊敬女人，是因为她们的内在
But not Lesbos. We accept other women for who they are inside!
真的吗？
You do? Seriously?
你有没有。。。有没有想过 和个女人一起做爱
Have you never... even thought, of being with another woman before?
没有，我根本就不知道两个女人能怎么做爱
No. I don't even know how two women... can make love.
除非他们只是互相磨来磨去还是什么
Unless they just kind of scissor or something.
欧耶，磨擦我， Xerxes!
Ohh yeah! Scissor me, Xerxes!
欧，感觉真是太棒了！
Ohh, that feels so supercool!
- 耶，摩擦! - 欧，我是个全新的女人!
- Yeah, scissor! - Ohh, I'm a new woman!
故事就是这样，蕾丝堡被保住了
And so it was that Lesbos was saved.
波斯人同意保持蕾丝堡原封不动
The Persians had agreed to leave it a lesbian bar,
就像没有个女同性恋能离开鸡尾酒一样
for no dyke should be without cocktails.
- 谢谢你所做的一切, Xerxes. - 不，谢谢你，朋友
- Thanks for everything, Xerxes. - No. Thank you, friend.
嘿，你现在不是应该在学校教书吗?
Hey, aren't you supposed to be teaching school right now?
学校雇了一个代课老师替代我
The school hired a substitute to cover for me.
所以捏，要求两个分数之和,
Hand so to find the sum of the two fractions,
你必须先求出最小公分母.
zhyou must always check for the lowest common denominator.
是的，是的
S? S? Yes. Yes. S?
这些人教的真好
These guys are pretty good.
耶，我想我终于实习学到点东西了
Yeah. I think I'm actually learning something.
双语合成 Lv&daisy